{
    "subject": "resource/Irving_Gordon",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Irving Gordon was born in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9125932455062866,
            "question": "What state was Irving Gordon born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8953052163124084,
            "question": "Where was Irving Gordon born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7185202240943909,
            "question": "Which country is considered Irving Gordon's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6912083029747009,
            "question": "What nationality was Irving Gordon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5107630491256714,
            "question": "What is Irving Gordon known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4490080773830414,
            "question": "Was Irving Gordon a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3398129940032959,
            "question": "In what year did Irving Gordon die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3145400881767273,
            "question": "Is Irving Gordon still alive today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29415762424468994,
            "question": "Where did Irving Gordon live most of his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14117473363876343,
            "question": "Did Irving Gordon write any famous songs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Irving Gordon was born in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9298_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Irving Gordon live most of his life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9298_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Irving Gordon still alive today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9298_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Irving Gordon die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9298_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9298_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9298_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9298_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9298_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9298_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9298_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9298_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9298_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9298_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9298_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Irving Gordon was born in the United States.\" Specifically, both files mentioning Irving Gordon state he was born in Brooklyn, New York, which is part of the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}